AYOBAMI — ADEOLU

■ UI/UX DESIGNER

+2347087980073 | SOJIADEOLU1@GMAIL.COM Dribbble.com/emmacreative | Lagos

ABOUT

UI/UX designer with 3+ years experience working as visual designer, branding expert and Interaction Designer. I've had the privilege of working on creative teams for companies and start ups on freelance, remote and full time basis and I have carried out several projects on small and large scales.

I am a team player, I can leverage on proven achievements, working knowledge of design softwares and methodology to deliver professionally as expected.

SKILLS

Figma	Adobe XD	Keynote
Adobe Illustrator	Framer	Sketch
Photoshop	Invision	HTML/CSS

TRAINING/COURSES

STUTERN GRADUATE ACCELERATOR

COMPLETED

EDUCATION

2013 - 2018

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE

OBAFEMI AWOLOWO UNIVERSITY

HOBBIES

Photography	Traveling	Movies
Music	Metaverse	Meditation

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan. 2021 - Present

SUMO-SOFT

PRODUCT DESIGNER

- Work with engineering and product stakeholders to design, prototype and validate new and existing products
- Uphold standard design practices by creating and maintaining design systems and clearly communicating the rationale behind UX designs
- Executed user research and visual design for the e-commerce web and mobile app (iOS and Android).

Jun. 2019 - Dec. 2020

NATURES OWN WONDER

PRODUCT DESIGNER

- Wireframed user flows, user stories and user interfaces of several end-to-end mobile and web apps.
- Designed 2 fin-tech applications, 3 e-commerce marketplaces, 1 learning management systems, and over 12 corporate websites and landing pages.

Mar. 2019 - May 2019

SCELLOO - INTERSHIP

PRODUCT DESIGNER

- Arranged the end-to-end user research and user interface design of 3 flagship enterprise products as well as the company's 1st ever design system.
- Worked effectively with the design team towards the execution of user research, user testing and creation of wireframes, visual design, flows and prototypes for web and mobile apps.

Jan. 2019 - June 2020

VORTEX247

DIGITAL DESIGNER

- Created websites using WordPress CMS and handled copywriting for landing pages, email newsletters, online advertisements, blog posts and search engine optimization.
- Reduced the company's marketing budget by 18% by creating and impementing growth hack strategies.